Let's go grab them up! The Dragon Balls!
Tsukamo ze! Doragon Booru
One of the most thrilling secrets in the world
Sekai de itto suriru na himitsu
Let's go seek them out! The Dragon Balls!
Sagaso ze! Doragon Booru
One of the most delightful miracles in the world
Sekai de itto yukai na kiseki
This life is one big treasure island
Kono yo wa dekkai takarajima
It's the truth!
Now more than ever, Adventure!
So sa ima koso adobencha!
The love of a pounding chest is GISSIRI
Mune waku-waku no ai ga GISSIRI
Multi-colored dreams rain down DOSSARI
Iro toridori no yume ga DOSSARI
Somewhere in this world, they are glowing
Kono yo no doko ka de hikatte 'ru
Let's go on out there and find them, boy
Soitsu mitsuke ni yuko ze BOY
All the while pounding on mutants and monsters
Yokai henge mo buttobashi
And we'll fly through the day on our cloud machine as well!
Kumo no mashin de kyo mo tobu no sa
Let's fly, fly, fly, how mysterious
Let's fly, fly, fly makafushigi
Charging through the sky, while we overcome mountains!
Sora o kakenuke yama o koe
Let's try, try, try, such an adventure
Let's try, try, try, daiboken
Our strange little journey now begins!
Fushigi na tabi ga hajimaru ze
Let's get them in hand! The Dragon Balls!
Te ni irero! Doragon Booru
One of the most formidable gambles in the world
Sekai de itto tegowai chansu
Let's go chase them down! The Dragon Balls!
Oikakero! Doragon Booru
Some of the most enjoyable drama in the world
Sekai de itto ikashita dorama
This life is one big treasure island
Kono yo wa dekkai takarajima
It's the truth!
Now more than ever, Adventure!
So sa ima koso adobencha!
Goku! Only the Basho Fan can put these flames out!
In order to put out the mysterious flames that have surrounded Gyumao's castle,
Goku and Chichi set out to find the Basho Fan,
armed only with a single hint
Fortuneteller Baba gave them: "octagon".
Hearing from an elderly scientist that the Basho Fan was on Ice Mountain,
which the Fire-Eating Bird is too afraid to get near,
the two made their way north. But...
"All Thanks to Chichi's Wife-Training"
What a beautiful mountain...
Why do you suppose the
Fire-Eating Bird won't get near it?
Help!
So cold...
W-Who are you?!
I'm... Goku...
I'm... his wife...
I'm the Octagon Woman.
Octagon... Woman?
So then, that means...!
Yeah! The Basho Fan must be on that mountain!
--We did it!
--Yeah!
So cold...!
You brought that girl all the way here from Mt. Frypan?
You mean I wasn't supposed to bring Chichi with me?
Of course you weren't!
That mountain has been called
Mt. No-Women-Allowed for ages!
What's that mean?
It means the curse will be set off whenever a woman goes up it!
So then that huge blizzard happened because of me?
Exactly what business do you two have on that mountain anyway?
We're looking for the Basho Fan.
The Basho Fan?
Supposedly, it can blow out any fire at all.
A fan that can blow out any fire at all...?
Do you know anything about it, ma'am?
No, I've never heard of it before...
But your name's Octagon.
Eh?
Fortuneteller Baba-san said it was somewhere relating to an octagon.
You misheard me. I'm not the "Octagon Woman"...
I'm the "Teeth-All-Gone Woman"!
So the Basho Fan isn't up there?
Where could it be?
Cheer up, young man!
Your goal is to put a fire out, correct?
There's something on the mountain that can do just that!
Really?
Can you tell us what it is?
The snow that falls on the mountain!
That snow is so cold, it can freeze even fire!
Snow that can freeze fire?
Goku-san! If we could just take some of that snow back with us...
Right!
This time, I'll go alone!
It's up to you, Goku-san!
--Can he borrow this, ma'am?
--Sure.
Goku-san!
Kinto Un!
The soup was great, ma'am!
Let's go!
Be careful!
Is he a good husband?
You bet! He's the best in the world!
And are you a good wife to him...?
W-We're still just newlyweds...
Do you want to be a good wife to him?
I want to be the best wife in the whole world!
Is that so?
Shall we start, then?
Pilaf-sama.
Might that be the northern mountain we're looking for?
I don't see 'em anywhere.
What do you think this Basho Fan thing they're looking for is, anyway?
They're trying really hard to find it!
It could be even greater than the Dragon Balls themselves!
With it in hand, I bet you could conquer the world for sure this time!
Mai! Keep us going forward, will ya?!
We've suddenly been caught up in a strange cloud...!
Uh oh! We're falling!
Hold on, Chichi!
I will bring it back!
Pull!
Pull harder or we'll all be stranded up here!
So cold...
It's so cold out here, even these robots might break!
Hey, you guys!
What're you doing?
--What the...?!
--Huh?
You!
Pilaf-sama!
Hey.
Why, you...! Now look what you've done!
--Eh?
--Pilaf-sama! Look out!
Pilaf-sama!
T-The fire froze...
This is so cold!
Wow! This can definitely put out that fire!
Clean this room,
this room,
and this room.
If you need water, you'll find a lake if you go through the forest
and continue past the next two valleys. Got it?
You don't have any plumbing?
Nope.
Aha! After all this time,
I finally got you cornered!
After all this time? We just saw each other at the volcano!
O-Oh, yeah...
Whatever! Just hand over the Basho Fan thingy!
Shuu! Mai! Get him!
Eh? But that's suicide...!
Pilaf-sama! Do we even have any way to stand up to him?!
No!
So what should we do?!
How come you guys know about the Basho Fan?
What's it matter? Take this!
Say...
Get him with everything you got!
Alright, then! You can have this back!
Scared you!
Hey.
Aren't you a girl?
T-That's right! Got a problem with that?!
--Hey...
--W-What?!
You know, they say that whenever a girl goes up this mountain...
What do you think you're doing, you moron?!
...the curse takes effect.
Curse?
Whenever a girl comes up, a blizzard shows up to freeze them...
W-What?!
Yeah, right!
Mai! Get over here!
Yes, sire. What can I do for you?
Roll down the mountain!
What was that?
I'm conducting an experiment! Hurry it up!
I-It's true!
That's it!
Chichi! Goku!
Hurry up with the Basho Fan!
How can I expect to be a good wife for Goku-san if I can't even do this?
Carrying the snow'll be a cinch if it's in snowball form!
Here he comes!
Why aren't you firing?!
Won't it just freeze again?
Don't worry! The blizzard's over!
--Fire!
--Huh?
You're still here?
Fire! Fire!
Huh?
Pilaf-sama...! You're terrible!
Oh, you're back! I'm so glad!
Don't assume you've won just yet!
Shuu! Mai! Time for our last resort!
Run away!
I brought you some tea, ma'am!
Oh, thanks.
You raise bees?!
Did you clean the house?
Yes, I'm all done.
Shoo!
Did you need anything else?
It would be really nice of you if you cleaned the garden!
Sure! Where might the garden be?
This entire forest is my garden!
This entire forest...?!
That's right! Here.
The dustpan's in the back!
Old man Gyumao!
Hold on just a little bit longer!
Here's the dustpan...
Huh? It feels like it's getting lighter for some reason...
It'll be all gone if I don't hurry!
Not too shabby...
Huh? What?
Get away!
What's going on...?
This did that?
Could this dustpan be the...?
This is it, ma'am! The Basho Fan!
What?
I found that thing lying on the beach a long time ago.
So the Basho Fan really was in an octagon place!
Just like Fortuneteller Baba said!
This is so great!
H-Hey, now...!
I haven't gotten very far, and already this is all that's left...
Chichi's gonna be so disappointed...
Goku-san!
I found the Basho Fan!
Let's hurry back to my dad!
Really?!
It's the Basho Fan, all right!
No doubt about it!
We'll take that!
You...!
Looks like I get the last laugh!
Give it back!
Don't move!
Move and I'll cut it in two!
Dammit...!
Pilaf-sama.
Is that grubby fan really worth anything?
Hey! Girl!
What?!
What sort of pan is that?
It's a fan!
Whatever! Just tell me already!
You'll find out if you swing it!
Oh, yeah?
Hey, Shuu! Give it a swing!
Right!
Goku-san! The Basho Fan is amazing!
Okay! Let's go, Chichi!
Take care, ma'am!
Hold on.
Take this with you.
What is it?
Honey made by my bees.
It's an extremely rare honey made by bees that live in octagonal beehives!
Octagonal beehives?
I have faith you'll become a great wife!
That honey might come in handy someday!
It has all sorts of uses, you see!
Thank you, ma'am!
Have a happy marriage!
Get outta here! Get, I say!
Haven't you found it yet?!
Chichi! Goku!
Chichi! I can't die until you've put this wedding gown on!
Damn it!
Dad! We brought the Basho Fan!
Everything's going to be okay!
Great! You brought it!
Old man Gyumao!
Hold on tight to something or you'll get blown away!
Got it!
Goku-san!
Alright!
It's out!
He did it!
Goku-san! The fire's back...!
Damn it!
I'll try again!
No matter how many times it takes,
I'll keep swinging until it goes out!
Rain!
--Rain!
--It might go out now!
Flames still surround Gyumao's castle.
Chichi!
Goku!
Dad!
Will Goku and Chichi be able to put out these mysterious flames,
which not even the
Basho Fan can extinguish?!
Come along, fantasy
Oide fantaji
I enjoy a mystery
Suki sa misuteri
Don't you go hiding your youth!
Kimi no wakasa kakusanai de
Wanting to perform the mysterious
Fushigi shitakute
Wanting to pursue the adventure
Boken shitakute
Everyone is itching to go!
Dare mo min'na uzu-uzu shite 'ru
If you act like an adult and give up
Otona no furi shite akiramecha
You'll never unravel the mystery of the miracle!
Kiseki no nazo nado tokenai yo
Go on and try to live even more wild and strong!
Motto wairudo ni
motto takumashiku ikite goran
I'll give you a romance,
I'll give you a romance
Romantikku ageru yo
If you will show me your true courage
Honto no yuki misete kuretara
I'll give you a romance,
I'll give you a romance
Romantikku ageru yo
I'll give your pounding heart a glittery, shining dream!
Tokimeku mune ni
kira-kira hikatta yume o ageru yo
Heya! It's Goku!
Damn it! Why won't it go out?!
Goku-sa, how about we go to Mt. Gogyo like Fortuneteller Baba suggested?
Huh? Where did you guys come from?!
--Outta the way!
--Monsters!
Damn it! We're so close to finding out this fire's secret!
Next time on Dragon Ball:
"Hurry, Goku! The Mystery of Mt. Gogyo"
Don't miss it!
Next Time
"Hurry, Goku! The Mystery of Mt. Gogyo"