Welcome to Polar Bear's Café!
Panda
Chilling and eating bamboo
grass is the best thing ever.
Hey now.
Look at you, being so lazy
so early in the day.
You're in the way of my cleaning.
Scoot.
Okay.
Seconds please, Mom.
Exactly what do you have
planned for your future?
Jeez...
Could we not talk about my future
when I'm relaxing?
If you have so much time to relax,
you could go look for a part-time job.
I'm too busy relaxing,
so I'll do it later.
Don't try to suck me up!
Jeez...
I wonder why Mom can't understand
how much time relaxing takes up.
Part Time Jobs!!
WORK KING
Excuse me,
which of these will have jobs
where I can get paid to do nothing?
I don't think there is one.
Really?
If I really have to work,
I'd prefer a really fancy job.
Oh!
This looks good.
Yes?
Oh, hi, my name is Panda.
You're advertising a part-time
position for a designer, right?
Yes, we are.
Do you have experience?
No, none.
Are you able to use a computer mouse?
Not at all!
I'm not very good with detailed work.
I see.
Do you have anything you're good at?
Yes, I do!
I'm good at eating bamboo grass,
and zoning out while lying down.
Huh?  Hello?
Oh, hello?
You're also advertising a position for
an interior coordinator, right?
Uh, yes.
What, exactly, is an
interior coordinator?
There you are being lazy again.
Did you find a part-time job?
There aren't any!
Weren't there openings at
the convenience store?
The convenience store?
They have too many things.
I won't be able to remember them all!
Don't try to suck me up!
Jeez.
I think I'll wander around outside.
Huh?  A string.
Could you get it?
Sure.
Got it!
Thank you!
Oh my.
Stay right there.
Hey, wait!
Wow, I didn't know there
was a café here.
Hello.
Welcome to Polar Bear's Café.
Table for one, sir?
Oh, well, I'm not exactly a custo—
Please have a seat anywhere you like.
O-Okay!
May I take your order?
Let's see...
Do you have bamboo?
We don't have any bamboo.
Then could I get bamboo grass?
We don't have bamboo grass either.
Then I'll have an iced coffee.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Polar Bear.
Do you ever get too many
point cards in your wallet?
You collect points, Mr. Penguin?
Yep.  Oh, could I get
another café mocha?
Seconds (okawari).
What?
Those would be sunflowers (himawari).
B Meal
That would be the
daily special (higawari).
That would be
splitting logs (makiwari).
That's splitting a watermelon (suika wari).
Seconds, please.
Here's your café mocha.
You know, if it weren't for all
the puns in this café...
By the way, I heard you were
looking for a part-timer?
Yes, I'm short-staffed.
Are you interested, Mr. Penguin?
Who, me?
I wonder if I could handle being
a customer and a part-timer.
Just kidding.  I have about
four interviews lined up.
Oh.  And here I was
actually considering it.
Could I have an interview, too?
I was also thinking of working part-time.
Would you like an interview?
What?!
Interview in Progress
Well then, will the first
applicant please come up.
Yes!
I'm Badger.
Let's see...  Would you be
able to work the hall?
Yes!  You can leave the holes to me!
I'm a pro at digging holes!
Er, "hall," not "hole."
Next applicant, please.
Here.
I'm... Giant... Tortoise...
Are you able to carry orders?
Yes.
Here we go...
Definitely taking his time.
Please let me work about
a hundred years.
Er, I don't think that'll be possible.
I'm Mandrill.
I'm very good at eating.
Not exactly what we're looking for.
I'm Anteater.
I-I can intimidate!
That's it?
Seems so.
Will the last applicant step up, please.
Okay!
My name is Panda.
Nice to meet you.
Finally a decent candidate.
Is there anything you're
good at, Panda?
Yes!
I'm very good at lying around
and eating bamboo grass.
Huh?
Er, let's see...
Are there any specific conditions
you'd like to request?
Two days a week, please.
Hm, you'd prefer two days?
Oh, you mean I could just
work one day a week?
No, no.  I was hoping for
at least four days a week.
I definitely can't do that.
Oh, but...
if you pick me up, I'll come right away.
I have to come and get you?
Oh, of course not.
Only if I'm late.
You have every intention
of being late, don't you?
Just curious...
do you really intend to work?
Not really.
And the results are
none of you passed.
What?!
Are you really that surprised?
It seems, in the end...
...I wasn't able to find a part-timer.
That's too bad.
You're still here?!
If I go home,
my mom will try to suck me up.
S-Suck you up?
Yep.  Like "whirrr."
Pardon me,
I hate to interrupt you
during your interviews.
I would like to live in...
I'm sorry, you fail.
I don't think he meant
a live-in employee.
I would like to live in your yard.
He asked me if I would
bring him here.
What is your name, Miss?
Who, me?  It's Sasako.
Miss Sasako, you pass.
What?!
Polar
Bear's
Café
Hey, Mom.
I found a really neat café today.
It's called Polar Bear's Café.
What are you talking about?
Of course I know about it.
Huh?  You do?
It's been there for a really long time.
Right next door to us.
What?!
Panda's Search for Employment.
Hello, this is Polar Bear's Café.
Oh, hello.
This is Panda, who you
interviewed the other day.
Oh, the one who didn't pass.
I would like to place a delivery order.
I'm sorry, we don't do deliveries.
Even though you're right next door?
Not to mention we're
quite busy right now.
Aww...
What would it take for
you to make a delivery?
Hey.
Oh, hi, Mom.
Lying around again...
I was looking for a job.
Come on, you're right next door,
so make a delivery.
Please?
Waah, please don't suck me up!
Hello.
What would you like?
What would you like, Mr. Penguin?
Let's see...
I'll have the usual.
I'll have the usual!
What?!
Usual
He asked for...
the usual.
Leave it to me.
Here's your curry rice.
Apparently that wasn't it.
I knew it.
Hey, now...
Excuse me,
do you not have any bamboo
or bamboo grass?
We do not.
Then could I get an iced coffee?
You were looking for a
part-time job, weren't you?
They have something like this:
Looking for tuna boat crewmen!
We will gladly accept
those with experience!
Intense physical labor!
How about it?
No way!  Not to mention, I can't swim!
I think this one is better.
The zoo is accepting applicants
without experience.
We will gladly accommodate work days.
"Please give us a call.
The Petting Zoo."
You should totally go
with the tuna boat.
Mr. Polar Bear...
The zoo, huh?  That sounds fun!
Let's see, so you're looking to
work two days a week?
Yes.
Then would you be interested in
the position of "panda"?
Huh?
We have one full-time panda,
but we're also looking to
fill a part-time slot.
When you say "panda," you do
mean that panda, right?
Are you not interested?
In that case, we are looking for
an Asian black bear and a gorilla.
I'll take the panda position.
I see.  Then please begin
coming next week.
I found a part-time job.
Really?  That's great to hear!
The tuna boat?
No way.  The zoo.
What part-time job are you
going to be doing at the zoo?
It's a secret.
Why are you so embarrassed?
Today's the day I start
my part-time job.
I'm so excited.
Hello again, my name is Handa.
We will have some preschool
visitors today.
Please give them a
little extra service.
Okay!
Service, huh?  You got it.
What should I be doing
the rest of the time?
Just act naturally.
Hey, Polar Bear.
How do you think Panda's doing?
I'm sure he'll get a huge
haul on the tuna boat.
You're not letting go of that, are you?
Oh, could I get a café mocha?
Um...
That would be a
body double (kagemusha).
Honestly, you don't have to do that.
Really?  Seven days a week?
You don't have a day off?
Well, I am a full-time panda.
But I do take about two
days off a month.
I'm so glad I'm part-time.
Well, it'll be a pleasure
working with you.
Same here.
Oh, by the way...
What's the matter?
Mr. Handa was saying...
...naturally.
is how I should act.
I see.
Is it something like this?
Does this look like I'm one with nature?
I don't think that's what he meant.
Or rather, that's very unnatural.
Well, you don't have to worry so much.
Just act like normal and you'll be fine.
Oh...
Ooh, pandas!
Look, children, pandas!
Oh, looks like the preschool
kids are here.
Let's give it our best.
O-Okay!
Look, the pandas are eating!
They sure are.
Look, the pandas are
playing on the slide!
Yes, they are.
Look, the pandas are rolling around!
Aren't they.
Is this what they consider service?
It's just for a little while longer.
All right, let's give it one more go!
A-All right!
Service, service...
Okay, everyone.
Let's go see the giraffes next.
Okay!
Right this way.
Service, service...
I totally fell asleep.
Why didn't you wake me up,
Mr. Full-Time Panda?
The zoo will now be closing.
Please come again.
Thank you for all your hard work today.
See you later!
Oh, hey, Panda.
Oh, you're all here?
Do you all know each other?
We're working part-time
at the zoo, as well.
Hey, Panda!  Over here!
The preschool kids were so cute today.
I over-exerted myself and passed out.
I can totally relate.
I worked so hard today.
Indeed, you did.
He looks so satisfied with himself,
I feel so fulfilled.
but apparently he slept half the time.
I know where you're coming from.
I guess that's "acting naturally" to him.
Panda's pretty shameless, isn't he?
Why don't you order something, Panda?
Let's see...
Huh?
What can I get for you?
Bamboo, please!
A large serving (oomori)!
Polar Bear, that's a gecko (yamori).
Oh, there there.
That would be babysitting (komori).
Miss Sasako retorted!
That would be harmonizing (hamori).
Hey, can I get my bamboo, already?
Next Time
Mr. Penguin, Mr. Penguin!
What do you think I'd look like
if I shaved off all my hair?
This isn't the time. We're supposed
to be doing the preview.
Then could you tell me three
bad traits about yourself?
Let's not do that either,
it'll bring the mood down.
Say something, Polar Bear.
Mr. Penguin's bad trait
is that he's bad with money.
Stop it!  Just finish already.
Okay.
Next time on "Polar Bear's Café,"
the last episode.  Enjoy!
I'm not letting you end with that!
Everyone's Café
"Polar Bear's Café" episode two!
Enjoy!